{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Renovation Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40382/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40382,"taskName":"Major Renovation - Multiple Rooms","taskDescription":"Remodel or Renovate One or More Rooms","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Renovation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":165,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"renovate laundry interior improvement renovations","textMessagingName":"Remod Renovate","rolloverLongDesc":"Larger scale renovation, repairs \u0026 fix ups where multiple trades are involved. There are specific categories for additions, home theaters, kitchens, baths, basements \u0026 handicap accommodation. If project doesn't fit those categories, use this general category. Note that remodeling implies major work, in which walls are moved or rebuilt. For minor alterations, see specific categories such as handyman, painting, tile work or carpentry.","rolloverShortDesc":"Larger scale renovation, repairs \u0026 fix ups where multiple trades are involved","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remodel or Renovate One or More Rooms.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Renovation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Major \u0026 Multi-Room Renovations","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Have a variety of small projects? How about hiring a ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"handyman?","bridgeTaskLinkId":15312,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Major Renovation - Multiple Rooms","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Major Renovation - Multiple Rooms","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Improvement Project","urlName":"Major-Renovation-Multiple-Rooms","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Renovation Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"renovate, improvement, renovations, makeover, build, remodeling, home, remodelers, renovating, remodel, addition, renovation, contractor, general, gut, finish, bedroom, den, attic, rehab, conversion","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":676,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40382/":{"taskOID":40382,"originalTaskOID":40382,"setID":676,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502445,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17573,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remodel / update the entire home","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update the entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17574,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17575,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","answerDisplayText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17576,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel as part of home addition","answerDisplayText":"Remodel as part of home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5336,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms to be Remodeled","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the rooms that will be part of your remodel.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3478,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502445,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17573,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remodel / update the entire home","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update the entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17574,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17575,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","answerDisplayText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17576,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel as part of home addition","answerDisplayText":"Remodel as part of home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17573,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remodel / update the entire home","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update the entire home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17574,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17575,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","answerDisplayText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17576,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel as part of home addition","answerDisplayText":"Remodel as part of home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5336,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms to be Remodeled","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the rooms that will be part of your remodel.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3478,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3478,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}